hashire motto kaze no mukou he
Corra o mais rápido possível contra o vento!
chiheisen wa kimi wo yonderu
O Horizonte está o chamando-o
hateshinai daichi ni umareta hi kara
Desde que tu nasceu nesta terra sem fim
ikiru koto wa sousa bouken
Sua vida será uma grande aventura!
tabidate reo sabanna koete
Embarque, Leo, para além da savana!
tatakau tabi kitto tsuyoku nareru
As dificuldades de sua jornada o tornarão mais forte.
saa reo kokoro wo moyase ima
Vai, Leo, coloque o seu coração em chamas!
sagashiteita jibun ni
Continue a busca do seu verdadeiro eu
deau hi made yukunda
Até o dia que se encontrarem!
Episódio 21
De volta ao lar
É o Bubu...
Ele voltou...
Por favor!
Alguém me ajude!
Socorro!
Depressa!
Saia daqui!
Ei, você parece
ameaçador?
Eu só estava me divertindo um pouco.
Não é, Toto?
Mas é claro, Bubu.
Se isso for verdade, você não acha que foi um pouco exagerado?
Tudo bem, Já terminamos por aqui. Vamos vazar daqui.
Saiam do meu caminho!
Abram caminho para o Bubu!
Agora você está a salvo.
O senhor salvou minha vida.
Muito obrigado.
Acho que nunca
a vi antes...
Bom, eu vim para a Selva de Panja porque ouvi dizer que era um lugar tranquilo...
I traveled so far, and now...
This has become
Bubu's Jungle now.
No, that is not true.
This is Panja's Jungle,
and it always has been.
B-But...
I understand... but in times like these, we alone must uphold the laws.
To me, at least, there's no
replacement for Panja's Jungle.
I guess you're right.
It's the least we can do.
If you're careful of Bubu,
it'll still be safer than outside the jungle.
See you around.
Thank you. I'll do just that.
If nothing changes, this jungle
might just become Bubu's one day...
Leo... when are
you coming back?
Leo, your time has come.
You must protect the jungle.
You must come back... soon...
Come back with your
new-found strength and skills.
If I can just get
past that jungle...
Panja's Jungle.
My friends' jungle.
H-Hey, look at that!
Wait, is that...
Leo! It really is you!
You're finally home, Leo!
I've got to spread the word!
What?! Leo's come home?!
Really?! He's back to save us?!
Listen! I've got big news!
Leo's come home!
Hooray! Finally, someone who can show Bubu who's boss!
Leo's come to
protect the jungle!
He's sure to keep us safe!
I can finally get some sleep.
Hold it!
L-Leo?!
Leo's come home!
This is Panja's Jungle.
Or did you forget about the laws, Bubu?
What?! I can't believe someone who broke the laws can preach like that!
Anyway, we were
just playin' around.
Panja's Jungle is so peaceful,
so I was just getting in a little exercise.
It should be clear that
I was just playing around.
Isn't that right?
Well...
What's wrong?
You callin' me a liar?
You have nothing to fear!
This is Panja's Jungle.
It's a jungle for everyone!
Be brave and tell me
what really happened!
Yeah! Go ahead, spit it out!
You know what happens to
those who stay quiet, don't ya?!
Bubu's telling the truth.
Th-That's right...
This isn't going to work...
If only... if only they weren't so...
You heard it, Leo!
Or do you have more objections?!
No...
Hey, wait! Where do
you think you're going?!
Turning tail again?!
Leo...
Leo can't save us...
I must protect my home.
I must protect Panja's Jungle!
Leo, you must protect this place.
Harness your strength and protect
Panja's Jungle from this fearsome power.
Great Mother... I feel like... I finally
have the power to protect this jungle.
And I'll do all that I can
to get even stronger...
That's ridiculous!
Leo would never run
away from Bubu!
But that's what
everyone's been saying.
Where is Leo?
The flycatcher said
he was near the ruins.
What do we say him?
We'll ask him to
deal with Bubu!
Leo isn't scared of Bubu!
I think that too.
Alright, let's go.
Leo! Leo!
Coco...
Leo! It's you, Leo!
Leo! Why didn't you come find us?!
You didn't need to be so distant.
I'm sorry. Do you think... do you
think we can ever be friends again?
No way!
We never stopped being friends.
So we can't be friends again.
Thank you... Coco...
Leo!
Leo! Leo!
Tony!
Leo!
Where have you been?!
Leo, I heard something
strange about you...
Someone said you
ran away from Bubu!
Of course, I don't
believe a word of it!
Neither do I.
And we're all here because
we have a favor to ask you.
You see, we'd like
you to stop Bubu!
You're the only one who's
strong enough to fight him!
Leo's gotten so strong!
I bet he'll beat Bubu paws-down!
Isn't that right, Leo?
But it's true...
The rumors about me are true.
And that's not all...
I shouldn't be fighting anyone here
in Panja's Jungle. Not even Bubu.
But...
And even if I did defeat him,
I'd be no better than he is.
And what's wrong with that?
No. If I did that, I wouldn't deserve
to be back in Panja's Jungle.
Didn't I tell you?
Leo's gone soft. He can't
protect the jungle anymore.
It doesn't matter what we say.
Let's just go.
Leo...
Can't you...
Can't you do something?!
Sorry...
Goodbye, Leo...
Goodbye...
It would just
become Leo's Jungle...
I understand... I understand, Leo...
I know what you're
trying to tell them...
Man, you really can't beat
the meat here in Panja's Jungle.
And there's nothing better than
eating it all up behind everyone's backs!
Good thing I followed Bubu.
Now I get to share the benefits...
Well, it's not like he leaves much
for me anyway, but whatever.
I wish he'd just take
over the place already.
Ah, well. It's probably smarter to
make everyone lower their guard first.
Having your food within reach
like this it ain't half-bad, y'know?
Hold on! Wait for me!
Where are you going?!
We just can't stay here...
What, you think it's
any better outside?
He's right.
Why are you leaving?
Why renounce your own home?
But this has already
become Bubu's Jungle.
Then why don't you
try taking it back?
We can't...
Not without Leo...
Why must you rely on Leo?
Have you even tried to
stand up to Bubu yourselves?
O-Of course we haven't.
We'd be fighting a losing battle.
Are you sure about that?
Have you ever considered
how many of us there are?
You're saying we should
all take a stand against Bubu?
But, even then, we're still
no match for his claws.
But we have to
project the jungle!
Well, say we went
through with it,
we'd still be breaking the laws,
then we'd be no better than Bubu.
That there is the problem.
Anyway, shouldn't we
at least think it over?
Perhaps, the issue
isn't with his claws,
but of fighting him
without breaking the laws.
Fighting him without
breaking the laws...
Bubu!
Wh-What on earth is going on?!
I have no idea!
It's getting closer!
We have to get away from here!
Could this be
Leo's first move?
What is this?!
This way!
Good job! We've got 'em cornered,
just like we planned!
Come on, everyone!
Let's go fight for our jungle!
They're all taking a stand!
All so they can protect their jungle!
Alright! We're almost at the cliff!
Keep it up!
I don't know what you've been thinking, but what's all this about?!
You think you can
defy the mighty Bubu?!
Leo... where are you?!
B-Bubu, we're here to uphold the laws of Panja's Jungle!
And if you don't like it,
y-you can just leave!
So you think there's
strength in numbers?
Fine, I'll take you all on!
This is Panja's Jungle!
We will uphold its laws!
Oh, really? Well,
I've taken a liking to this jungle!
So there's no way I'm leaving.
And I have no intention
of upholding the laws...
Alright, listen up!
From this day forward,
this is Bubu's Jungle!
I take it we have
no objections...
Panja's Jungle doesn't
belong to anyone!
Leo!
I just knew you'd
come back, Leo!
- Leo!
- Leo's back!
Leo, I can't wait to see
how much you've grown.
You gonna fight? Or will you
just run away like last time?
I will not break our laws!
You coward! How will you protect
the jungle without breaking its laws?!
We'll use our determination!
Everyone's determination, united!
Leo...
It doesn't matter to me
if you uphold the laws or not.
I just want to make
an example out of you!
L-Leo...
- Leo!
I swear I'll uphold
the laws... Bubu!
- Leo!
You have just witnessed
the true strength of Bubu!
Leo!
Let go of Leo! If you won't
abide by the laws, then leave!
Leave!
Leave, Bubu!
That's right! Leave!
- Leave!
- Let go of Leo!
- Get out of our jungle!
Let go of Leo!
- Let him go!
- Let go of Leo!
Let him go!
I will uphold the laws, Bubu!
- Uphold our laws!
- Let Leo go!
Uphold our laws!
This is it... this is everyone's
determination, united!
- Let Leo go!
- Uphold our laws!
Fine, I'll leave!
I'll leave your pathetic jungle!
We did it!
- We did it!
Leo! Leo, hang in there!
Leo.
We protected our jungle!
We did it... we all protected
our jungle together, right?
That's right, Leo!
That's exactly what we did!
Everyone... will you... will you let me
come back and be your friend again?
Of course we will, Leo!
I already told you, didn't I?
We've always been friends.
Thank you, Coco.
Thank you, everyone!
Reunion
Episode 22
Preview
Poachers have
returned to the jungle.
And for everyone
to protect it...
Somehow,
I end up saving a human.
Next time on Jungle Emperor:
Episode 22: Reunion.
I... remember this human...
boy meguriaete yokatta
Que bom nos conhercemos
Script Original: @InkaSubs
Tradução PT-BR: @EmeraldFansubs
boy konna hiroi sekai de
Nesse mundo vasto
kimi to ikiru ichinichi wa
Um único dia contigo
kitto asu mo kirameku hazu nano
Fará um amanhã mais brilhante.
ima orenji iro no hi ga shizumu kara
Neste momento, o sol está se pondo.
futari no shiruetto yuubae ni nare
E Nossas silhuetas brilham no pôr do sol
mabushii yuubae ni nare
O quão brilhante é o pôr do sol